christiansunite.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy

       **AT CHRISTIANSUNITE.COM** , we fully recognize the value of your privacy, and we make protecting your privacy our highest priority. Under no circumstances will any advertiser or third party be disclosed any member - specific information, except as required by law. 

       These policies are in effect for the newsletters, forums, opt-in announcement lists, webmaster tools, or in any other area owned and operated by ChristiansUnite where personal information may be collected. 

       Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

       When you sign up for the ChristiansUnite discussion forum, newsletter, or any webmaster utility, your name or alias is recorded solely for purposes of maintaining your own account within these areas. This information is not used to monitor your activity, nor is it used to identify you outside the ChristiansUnite network. 

       We do not collect and evaluate any information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors. 

       We only disclose demographic information in aggregate, percentage terms and never disclose any personal information to any client or third party. 

       We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. From time to time, ChristiansUnite or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can NOT read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of ChristiansUnite's Network you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. 

       ChristiansUnite will ONLY disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

       1) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ChristiansUnite, 

       2) Protect and defend the rights or property of the ChristiansUnite Network of sites and related properties, or visitors to the ChristiansUnite Network of sites and related properties, 

       3) Identify persons who may be violating the law, the ChristiansUnite legal notice and Web site User Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the ChristiansUnite Network or its related properties, 

       By using the ChristiansUnite Network, you consent to the collection and use of information by ChristiansUnite as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it, but under no other circumstances will your private information be disclosed. 

       Personal information is information - such as your name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address - that can be used to uniquely identify you.
